Hey gas welcome back to my mother watch the video the
bike is standing in front of you I will not review it today
but this video is going to be very informative for you
this bike had
fallen you can say it had a
small accident so today we are taking it to
TVS service
center here we will take it through the insurance process and
tell you everything that was
damaged inside the vehicle,
see only one is broken, okay this one is
broken, look at this here on the camera
you will see scratches here you will see
scratches here look at this panel this is
broken this panel is broken there
are slight scratches in it too and this
plastic is broken the rest here
this thing is opened here okay there are
slight scratches on it there are slight
scratches here the leg guard band is broken
this thing and let's go to the back
you can see this silencer strip you have
read it completely brother there are
slight scratches here
now the thing to be seen is that the one which is for
insurance  What
process do the servicers follow and what parts do they change? The
process is that
as soon as your car meets with an
accident, you take it to the service
center. The first thing you have to do is check
where you bought the car from and what
insurance you got. Take it to their service
center and ask them whether
it is cashless or not. If it is cashless, then
you will have to pay the same file charges for
whatever is charged in the series. If it is
not cashless, then you will have to pay the same amount.
After one and a half months, the insurance company will credit the
money to your account. Now we are going to the
service center and we will see
what the surveyors identify on it
and what they say about
what things we will change in it and what not. In
what way is the insurance
beneficial or harmful for you. I will
tell you about that as well. I have a first party zero type car.
Right now, the car has run for 2000 km. If
anyone has this
power, then I will tell you about that.
I will ask them and get everything done.
Brother, the
PAN card, license is attached and the car is insured.  that the
RC is installed and you should apply your insurance,
okay, so all these things are installed, we are
waiting, it will be photocopied now, a
form has been given, after that we will check everything,
what is it, what is not, the
sound was not good, that is why
we have recorded this video again brother, this is it,
okay, look brother, this was installed, the car is
going, there are scratches on one light
and it is also breaking inside, this panel is bending, the
leg has become crooked here, the handle has become a little
high because from here, try
driving it once, if
two people are sitting in it, then you feel something slightly, the
car seems to be on the bottom, okay,
you check the rest, when you make the card,
tell us how many days for it, I am taking it for 15 days, 20 days,
maybe a month also, the car has the power here
and the entire process, the documents that are installed are installed by
us, Aadhar card,
PAN card, RC, insurance and driver's
license, okay, this is installed, now if there has been a
change in the panel inside it, we will tell you about that
and you will see this video, come on
brother, in the video today  I will put it in here, leave it,
I will put it later, what will happen now, one thing will be that
when we come to buy the car, then
whatever changes have been made, we will show you that too, so this was the
process till there,
okay, now when its card is also made,
see in the card, what you do and what you don't do, that will be
told, okay, so as and when whatever
updates come, we will keep telling you
and okay, there was no such special process which was very
big, but yes, there is one more thing,
whenever you buy a new bike or a car, then
one more thing is that brother, get the insurance done
from a good company, we had done it with S16, so there are
many forms to fill in it,
so that you can pay the ICC, their claims are done online, so
this is easier, so brother, I am
making this video, okay, so that there is
no problem in future, the bike remains the same as it was
and this will be shown in the evening video, someone is coming
tomorrow, we will pick it up later,
okay, what are the major changes in the parts, the
power, the
problem is that it is showing the top speed of 160, that's it,
just hit reset,
okay,
after doing it, it will change,
okay, get it
checked by the mechanic.  I will give it to you and they will also get the handle changed
if there is a problem with it then there is no
problem you can do as per your convenience and this leg
garden is fine, right?
[Music]
okay sir it
depends on the availability so that will be done
okay okay okay okay
brother its calculations are done it will be from a
good company so you do
n't have to read these forms you
come take a photo and make a claim like one of
my acquaintances did it for ko ko in that after taking a photo
they put 65 in the account can
you do it through story sir there are good
things too the other thing the
process of S 16 was a bit long rest sir
what comes what does the rest we have
made a video now we are leaving for
15 days but I will take time I have
explained the entire process in it
now we have started walking towards home